Ana Bollain

Front-end Developer





About me

Curious by nature, I define myself as persevering and resourceful. With great adaptability, my empathy, collaborative attitude and commitment make me a great team player.

Thanks to over 6 years of work experience in France and Spain, communicating in both English and French, I have mastered both project planning and stress management to meet client expectations with tight deadlines.

Soft skills

Teamwork **Empathy Problem Solving** Attention to detail Creative Thinking Responsiveness Adaptability Management

Proyectos

Rick & Morty 👄 Personal Project | React JS

Minion's Cards 👄 Team Project | Javascript

Breaking Bad C Personal Project | React JS

Legacy JS Code Upgrading 👄 Team Project | React & Node JS

Adalabers 👄 Personal Project | React JS

Whack Tartalo 👄 Personal Project | Javascript

Adatravellers (=) Team Project | HTML5 & CSS3

Experience

Front-end Developer

Bootcamp Adalab | Remote | Sept. 2022 - Dec. 2022

- > Layout: HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Responsive Design, Flexbox, CSS Grid.
- > Javascript (ES6) and creation of a SPA application with React.
- > Developing a basic REST API with Node JS and Express JS.
- > SQLite for creating and managing databases and EJS Template Engine.
- > Version control with Git.
- > Project development under SCRUM framework and Agile philosophy.
- > Development tools: Gulp, Visual Studio Code, Terminal, Zeplin.
- > Communication skills and team work: Slack, Github, Railway.

Partner Architect & Freelance Interior Designer

Freelance. Remote | March 2022 - Oct. 2022 Estudi Biga SCCLP. Barcelona | Sept. 2019 - March 2022 Katty Schiebeck. Barcelona | April 2019 - Oct. 2019

- > Management and development of projects as a team leader.
- > Coordination of all parties involved in project decision-making.
- > Design, illustration and 3D rendering of creative proposals.
- > Production of techinal and administrative documentation.
- > Adaptability to tight deadlines with high quality standards.

Architect & Interior Designer

Atelier du Pont. Paris | Jan. 2017 - March 2019 AWP. París | March 2016 - Oct. 2016

- > Contact with clients in oral presentations and project follow-up.
- > Analysis of commercial proposals and compliance with client's budget.
- > Contact with sales representatives for the prescription of materials.
- > Management and development of residential and hospitality projects.

Education

Intensive Front-end Development Bootcamp

Adalab | Remote | Sept. 2022 - Dec. 2022

Online Web Development Courses

Platzi | Remote | July 2022 - Sept. 2022 HTML5 & CSS3 | CSS Grid | Javascript | JS Engine (V8) & Browser

Basics of Web Development & Coding

Coursera. University of Michigan | Remote | April 2022 - June 2022

Master of Architecture

ETSAM. Polytechnic University of Madrid | Sept. 2008 - July 2015

Architecture & Landscape Exchange Program

KTH. Sweden | Erasmus | Sept. 2012 - July 2013

Technical Skills Languages

\bigcirc	HTML5	\bigcirc	Gulp	Spanish
\bigcirc	CSS3	\bigcirc	Git	Native
\bigcirc	Sass	\bigcirc	Agile	English
\bigcirc	Javascript	\bigcirc	Scrum	Professional. C1 Advanced (CAE)
\bigcirc	React JS	\bigcirc	InDesign	French
\bigcirc	Node JS	\bigcirc	Illustrator	Fluent
\bigcirc	SQLite	\bigcirc	Photoshop	Basque

Basque

Native, EGA